seeing-stars.com 2018-03-09

# Disclaimers

At _Seeing-Stars.com_ , we never ask for your name, address, email address or telephone number on any part of our website. If you email _us_ , we will never knowingly sell your name or email address to others, nor will we disclose such information to others unless you ask us to (unless required to by law.) If _you_ write _us_ , however, we may send you email of our own, which we believe you want to receive (due to your interest in this website) - replies to your questions & comments, or updates about what's new on the _Seeing-Stars_ website. We may also reserve the right to publish selected quotes from email that we feel would be informative for our readers (using only your first name). If you don't wish to receive updates or newsletters from us, just let us know (via email at [webmaster@seeing-stars.com](mailto:webmaster@seeing-stars.com)) and we will promptly remove your name from our mailing list. 

**Note** : If you mouse click on advertising banners, or on links to other sites, that click may well take you off the _Seeing-Stars.com_ website, to totally different websites which are not controlled by us. These other websites might collect personal information and/or use it ways different than we do. To be sure, you should review the Privacy Policy of these other websites. Some ads on the site may set cookies of their own.  

You may also want to review the Privacy Policy of Womens Forum, an ad agency which supplies most of the ads on this site.  

Their privacy policy, which they have asked me to post, follows:

> **Privacy Policy**
> 
> At **SITENAME** , we respect the privacy of the viewers who visit our communities and share their personal information with us. So we've designed our site and programs with their privacy in mind. Our Privacy Policy describes how we obtain, use and disclose non-public personal information about our viewers to our select marketing partners. You will be subject to the terms of this Policy if you register with us or use any of our services.
> 
> This Privacy Policy is subject to change.
> 
> **Information about All Visitors**
> 
> Unless otherwise noted in special promotions, **SITENAME** generally gathers information about its users collectively and only uses this data to determine how to improve the overall [experience](http://www.womensforum.com/site-terms-and-conditions.html) for our visitors and members. If this information is shared with our partners or sponsors, it is only in the aggregate, which enables them to better understand how Womensforum.com visitors use and enjoy our site and which resources are of primary interest to them.
> 
> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 
> 
> **Research**
> 
> **SITENAME** may research our users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration. We may do this to better understand and serve our visitors. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. **SITENAME** may share this aggregated data with select marketing partners.
> 
> **Information Usage**
> 
> In order to provide you with exemplary services, products, and the benefits of our selected partnerships, **SITENAME** displays multiple forms of advertisements from select partners. By better knowing our viewers, we are able to more effectively target content and sponsors offers to our viewers.
> 
> **SITENAME** uses an opt-in system before sharing user information with anyone. You always have the option of not providing permission for your information to be shared. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests.
> 
> **Third Party Data and Aggregated Data**
> 
> **SITENAME** may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.
> 
> **Third Party Advertising**
> 
> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.
> 
> **NAI Opt Out of Behavioral Advertising**
> 
> The NAI Opt-out Tool was developed in conjunction with our members for the express purpose of allowing consumers to "opt out" of the behavioral advertising delivered by our member companies. Please click here for further information: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
> 
> **Third Party Cookies**
> 
> In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "[cookie](http://www.womensforum.com/site-terms-and-conditions.html)" on your browser.
> 
> **Children**
> 
> We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and feel strongly about protecting the rights and privacy of children. As such, we do not collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of 13, and will remove personally identifying information about such minors from our system. We are compliant with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998. See this page for more information: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/coppa.htm
> 
> **Your IP Address**
> 
> We may note your IP address when you visit our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our web site, track user movements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We collect aggregate (anonymous) information on persons who access our site so that we can keep it up-to-date, useful and relevant to visitors.
> 
> **Cookies**
> 
> "Cookies" are files with information that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Womensforum.com uses cookies only to keep track of user I.D. information.
> 
> **Disclosure of Information**
> 
> **SITENAME** may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms of use or causing injury to, or interfering with, our rights, property, other users, or anyone else.
> 
> **SITENAME** may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our service to you.
> 
> **Your Consent**
> 
> By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by **SITENAME**. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the revised policy on this page so that you are always aware of any changes.
> 
> **Disclaimer**
> 
> Please be aware that no data transmitted over the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. Thus, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or information that is transmitted to you from our products, services or partners. Sometimes the information you disclose can be collected and used by others. If you post personal information that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
